# **Isaac Carnes**

## **Full Stack Web Developer**

Pittsburgh, PA 15206

Email: IsaacJDeveloper@gmail.com

LinkedIn: /Isaac-J-Carnes Github: /IsaacJCarnes

Portfolio: isaacjcarnes.github.io/ij-portfolio/

Imaginative Full-Stack Web Developer interested in creating fun responsive user experiences and effective compact code. Holds a certification in Full Stack Web Development. Driven code designer focussed on creative design and efficiency when developing.

#### **Technical Skills**

Languages: JavaScript ES6+, CSS3, HTML5, C# Technologies: SQL, NoSQL, GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL, Express, React, Node, Handlebars, jQuery, Bootstrap Core Concepts: Leadership, Flexibility, Communication, Integrity, Avid Learner, Responsibility

#### **Relevant Experience**

Psychology Student Researcher, Apr 2017–Feb 2019 Carnegie Mellon University, Pittsburgh, PA Work with a contracted developer and post-graduate students to develop a simple python game to relate decision making to motion tracking in the test subject.

#### **Additional Experience**

Technology Associate, Aug. 2021–Jan. 2022 Staples, Pittsburgh, PA

Shipment Coordinator, Jan. 2021–July 2021 VSMPO Tirus, Pittsburgh, PA

### **Projects**

Card Graphix | github.com/wl0194/card-graphix | card-graphix.herokuapp.com

- A heroku web app built with react that allows the user to create, customize and export their own business card.
- Responsible for team management, some page design, card creation functionality
- Heroku, React, Apollo JS, Cloudinary, Html2Canvas, js2pdf

Dog Endorsement Website | github.com/lsaacJCarnes/DogEndorsementWebsite | dog-endorsement-website.herokuapp.com

- A heroku web app built with node handlebars that allows the user to find local adoptable dogs using the petfinder api.
- Responsible for team management, page design, backend linking and api implementation
- Heroku, Handlebars, Petfinder API

Maze Game | github.com/lsaacJCarnes/MazeGen | isaacjcarnes.github.io/MazeGen

- A github pages web app that allows the user to play through a simple maze and save their times into their local storage.
- Responsible for team management and maze creation system
- Github Pages, Giphy API

#### **Education**

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development: University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, PA